One More Shot is a action, thriller film directed by James Nunn.
Following the attack on the black site in Poland, Navy SEAL Jake Harris is
ordered to escort terrorist suspect Amin Mansur to Washington D.C.
for interrogation.
Before the prisoner transfer process is complete, though, the airport is
attacked by a group of heavily armed, well-trained mercenaries.
Jake Harris, played by Scott Adkins.
Robert Jackson, played by Michael Jai White.
Jennifer Lomax, played by Alexis Knapp.
Niesha Mansur, played by Meena Rayann.
Amin Mansur, played by Waleed Elgadi.
Hooper, played by Hannah Arterton.
One More Shot (also known as One Shot 2) is a 2024 action thriller film.
It is a direct sequel to One Shot (2021), and is
followed by One Last Shot (2026).
The film was directed by James Nunn and starring Scott Adkins,
Michael Jai White, Alexis Knapp, and Tom Berenger.
Like the original, it is edited to appear as if
shot in a single, continuous take.
The film explores themes of affectation, hostile,
intense, antagonistic, appreciative.
The tone is intense.